Once You Hear It, It’s Too Late
The Confession is a horror film directed by Will Canon.
A woman finds her late father’s tape confessing to murder tied to an evil
force—now her son shows the same darkness, and she must fight to stop it.
Naomi Riley, played by Italia Ricci.
Grayson Phillips, played by Scott Mechlowicz.
Dylan Riley, played by Zachary Golinger.
Harling Guidry, played by Terence Rosemore.
The Piper, played by Justin Matthew Smith.
Luellen, played by Allie McCulloch.
Confessions of a Shopaholic is a 2009 American romantic comedy film based on the
first two entries in the Shopaholic series of novels by Sophie Kinsella.
Directed by P.
Hogan, the film stars Isla Fisher as the shopaholic
journalist and Hugh Dancy as her boss.
The film was released in theaters on February 13, 2009.
Despite being a box office success, it received negative reviews from
critics, though Fisher's performance received praise.
The film explores themes of grave, haunted house,
possession, tragic, possessed child.
The tone is dark.